Guide to the Duke University Chapel Recordings, 1954-2002 UA.17.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Recordings, 1954-2002; 1
  - Peter Storey - "When God Turns the Tide", 1990 June 17; 1701
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0186)
  - Thomas G. Long - "The Living Out of Dreams", 1990 June 24; 1702
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0493)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0187)
  - Paula E. Gilbert - "Marked for Life", 1990 July 01; 1703
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0494)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0188)
  - William Willimon - "Jesus' Vacation", 1990 July 08; 1704
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0495)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0189)
  - Elizabeth Achtemeier - "The Word of the Kingdom", 1990 July 15; 1705
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0496)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0190)
  - William Willimon - "Some Way to Run a Farm", 1990 July 22; 1706
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0497)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0191)
  - Jon Michael Spencer - "Neither Slave nor Freeman", 1990 July 29; 1707
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0498)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0192)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Eternal Optimists", 1990 August 05; 1708
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0499)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0193)
  - Harold C. Warlick, Jr. - "Power", 1990 August 12; 1709
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0500)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0194)
  - Wade P. Hure, Jr. - "A Long Robe with Flowing Sleeves", 1990 August 19; 1710
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0196)
  - William Willimon - "The Distance of God", 1990 August 26; 1711
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0501)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0195)
  - William Willimon - "Living Sacrifice", 1990 September 02; 1712
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0502)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0197)
  - William Willimon - "The Peril of Forgiveness", 1990 September 09; 1713
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0503)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0198)
  - William Willimon - "Justice", 1990 September 16; 1714
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0504)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0199)
    - Copy - VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0200)
  - William Willimon - "Hell Is for Accountants", 1990 September 23; 1715
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0505)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0201)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "The Mind of Christ", 1990 September 30; 1716
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0506)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0202)
  - William Willimon - "Be Imitators of Me", 1990 October 07; 1717
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0507)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0203)
  - William Willimon - "R.S.V.P.", 1990 October 14; 1718
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0508)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0204)
  - William Willimon - "Ordinary People", 1990 October 21; 1719
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0509)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0205)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "Thinking and Feeling the Faith", 1990 October 28; 1720
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0510)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0206)
  - William Willimon - "Who Are These?", 1990 November 04; 1721
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0511)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0207)
  - William Willimon - "The Day of the Lord", 1990 November 11; 1722
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0512)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0208)
  - William Willimon - "One Tough Master?", 1990 November 18; 1723
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0513)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0209)
  - Floyd Thompkins, Jr. - "Empty Jars and Bills to Pay", 1990 November 25; 1725
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0514)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0210)
    - Copy - VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0211)
  - William Willimon - "Now", 1990 December 02; 1726
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0515)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0212)
  - Dennis M. Campbell - "A Sower Went Forth" Founders' Day, 1990 December 09; 1727
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0516)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 48, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0213)
  - William Willimon - "More", 1990 December 16; 1728
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0517)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0214)
  - William Willimon - "Here", 1990 December 23; 1729
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0518)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0215)
  - William Willimon - "Los Angeles" Christmas Eve Service, 1990 December 24; 1730
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0519)
  - Carol Marie Noren - "Simeon and Anna", 1990 December 30; 1731
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0520)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0216)
  - Thomas G. Long - "The Irony of the Epiphany", 1991 January 06; 1732
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0521)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "A New Beginning", 1991 January 13; 1733
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0522)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0217)
  - Richard Lischer - "No Prophet Is Acceptable in His Own Country", 1991 January 20; 1734
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0523)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0218)
  - Roberta Hestenes - "Do People Really Change?", 1991 January 27; 1735
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0524)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0219)
  - William Willimon - "A Sign of the Times", 1991 February 03; 1736
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0525)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0220)
  - William Willimon - "Defying Chaos with God", 1991 February 10; 1737
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0526)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0221)
  - Henry H. Mitchell and Ella Pearson Mitchell - "A Man after God's Own Heart", 1991 February 17; 1738
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0527)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0222)
  - Ronnie E. Swain, Jr. - "Overcoming Fear", 1991 February 24; 1739
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0528)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0223)
  - William Willimon - "The Anger of Jesus", 1991 March 03; 1740
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0529)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0224)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Judgment and Grace", 1991 March 10; 1741
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0530)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0225)
  - William Willimon - "The Weight of Glory", 1991 March 17; 1742
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0531)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0226)
  - William Willimon - "Though He Was in the Form of God", 1991 March 24; 1743
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0532)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0227)
  - William Willimon - "Easter Fear" Easter Service, 1991 March 31; 1744
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0533)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0228)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Too Good to Be True?", 1991 April 07; 1745
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0534)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0229)
  - William Willimon - "Be Not Faithless, but Believing", 1991 April 14; 1746
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0535)
  - William Willimon - "Pursued by Mercy", 1991 April 21; 1747
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0536)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0230)
  - William Willimon - "The New Family", 1991 April 28; 1748
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0537)
  - Nancy Ferree - Clark - "Friends in Christ", 1991 May 05; 1749
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0538)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0231)
  - William Willimon - "The Poet and God's Way", 1991 May 10; 1750
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0539)
  - Eugene Taylor Sutton - "Quiet! The Church Is Being Born", 1991 May 19; 1751
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0540)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0232)
  - William E. Smith - "Must We Be Born Again?", 1991 May 26; 1752
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0541)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0233)
  - Barbara Brown Taylor - "Sabbath Time", 1991 June 02; 1753
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0542)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0234)
  - James Earl Massey - "Looking beyond Our Laments", 1991 June 09; 1754
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0543)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0235)
  - Robert W. Bailey - "Birthplace of Confidence", 1991 June 16; 1755
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0544)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0236)
  - Elizabeth Achtemeier - "Contingency, Chaos, and Christ", 1991 June 23; 1756
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0545)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0237)
  - John M. Stapleton - "The Ultimate Sovereignty", 1991 June 30; 1757
    - Original audiocassette (Box 34, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0546)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0238)
  - Ann I. Hoch - "Concealed in the Commonplace", 1991 July 07; 1758
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0547)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0239)
  - Julian M. Aldridge, Jr. - "Eyeing the Essentials", 1991 July 14; 1759
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0548)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0240)
  - Harold C. Warlick, Jr. - "The Things We Hide in Our Heart", 1991 July 21; 1760
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0549)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0241)
  - Gayle C. Felton - "Feeding the Hungry Crowd", 1991 July 28; 1761
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0550)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0242)
  - C. G. Newsome - "Living without Walls", 1991 August 04; 1762
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0551)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0243)
  - John Killinger - "Nothing if Not Radical", 1991 August 11; 1763
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0552)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0244)
  - Carol Marie Noren - "Half a Loaf", 1991 August 18; 1764
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0553)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0245)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "Leap or Stumble", 1991 August 25; 1765
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0554)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0246)
  - William Willimon - "The Inverting Promise", 1991 September 01; 1766
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0555)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0247)
  - William Willimon - "The Gracious Dream", 1991 September 08; 1767
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0556)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0248)
  - William Willimon - "The Fearful Meeting", 1991 September 15; 1768
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0557)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0249)
  - William Willimon - "The Night Visitor", 1991 September 22; 1769
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0558)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 49, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0250)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "Not According to Plan…", 1991 September 29; 1770
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0559)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0251)
  - William Willimon - "Public Sex", 1991 October 06; 1771
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0560)
  - William Willimon - "Divine Divestment", 1991 October 13; 1772
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0561)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0252)
  - William Willimon - "You Need a Good Priest", 1991 October 20; 1773
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0562)
  - Peter J. Gomes - "The Lively Oracles of God", 1991 October 27; 1774
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0563)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0253)
  - William Willimon - "Don't Think for Yourself", 1991 November 03; 1775
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0564)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0254)
    - Copy - VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0255)
  - Carol Marie Noren - "Widow's Might", 1991 November 10; 1776
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0565)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0256)
  - William Willimon - "The End of Religion", 1991 November 17; 1777
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0566)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 51, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0303)
  - Richard J. Mouw - "People of the Lamb", 1991 November 24; 1778
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0567)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0257)
  - William Willimon - "God Is Coming", 1991 December 01; 1779
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0568)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0258)
  - Hans J. Hillerbrand - "Preparing, Also for the Unexpected" Founders' Day, 1991 December 08; 1780
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0569)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0259)
  - William Willimon - "Good News - Repent", 1991 December 15; 1781
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0570)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0260)
  - William Willimon - "Jesus Goes to School", 1991 December 22; 1782
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0571)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0261)
  - William Willimon - Christmas Eve Service, 1991 December 24; 1783
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0572)
  - B. Maurice Ritchie - "High Profile for 'Low Sunday'", 1991 December 29; 1784
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0573)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0262)
  - The Caux Scholars Program, 1992; 1785
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0267)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "God's Surprises", 1992 January 05; 1786
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0574)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0263)
  - Joan Brown Campbell - "Eyes of Faith", 1992 January 12; 1787
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0575)
  - Samuel D. Proctor - "Setting in Order the Things That Are Wanting", 1992 January 19; 1788
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0576)
  - William Willimon - "The Lord of the Word", 1992 January 26; 1789
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0264)
  - Thomas G. Long - "Prophet without Honor", 1992 February 02; 1790
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0577)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0265)
  - Mark E. Grazman - "Moshe the Beadle", 1992 February 09; 1791
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0578)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0268)
  - William Willimon - "Tears Today, Laughter Later", 1992 February 16; 1792
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0579)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0269)
  - William Willimon - "A Religion for Losers", 1992 February 23; 1793
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0580)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0270)
  - Walter Brueggemann - "Re-Formed for Ministry", 1992 March 01; 1794
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0581)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0271)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "Nothing but the Essentials", 1992 March 08; 1795
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0582)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0272)
  - Charles L. Campbell - "Citizens of Heaven", 1992 March 15; 1796
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0583)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0273)
    - Copy - VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0274)
    - Copy - VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0275)
  - William Willimon - "God's Own Good Time", 1992 March 22; 1797
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0584)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0276)
  - David H. C. Read - "God Loves You—So What?", 1992 March 29; 1798
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0585)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0277)
  - William Willimon - "Love and Death", 1992 April 05; 1799
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0586)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0278)
  - William Willimon - "A Terrifying Tale", 1992 April 12; 1800
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0587)
  - Kammerer Prize Competition, 1992 April 17; 1801
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0266)
  - William Willimon - "An Idle Tale?", 1992 April 19; 1802
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0588)
  - Dennis Campbell - "Witnesses to the Things", 1992 April 26; 1803
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0589)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0279)
  - William Willimon - "The God of the Second Chance", 1992 May 03; 1804
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0590)
  - Debra K. Brazzel - "The Good Shepherd", 1992 May 10; 1805
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0591)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0280)
  - William Willimon - "1492 to 1992" Baccalaureate Service, 1992 May 15; 1806
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0281)
  - Margaret B. Via - "The Deepest of All Riddles", 1992 May 17; 1807
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0592)
  - William Willimon - "I'm Saved, You're Saved, Maybe", 1992 May 24; 1808
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0593)
  - David L. Bartlett - Sermon Untitled, 1992 May 31; 1809
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0594)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0282)
  - William Willimon - "We're All Here" Pentecost Service, 1992 June 07; 1810
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0595)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0283)
  - James L. Travis - "A Hope That Will Not Cheat", 1992 June 14; 1811
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0596)
    - Original VHS videocassette (Box 50, Video-cassette UA.17.01.0003 VHS-0284)
  - Ann I. Hoch - "Through Thick and through Thin", 1992 June 21; 1812
    - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette UA.17.01.0003 CS-0597)